Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube channel Stock
Time. In this video, we
will talk about some stocks whose market
news is being seen.
Brokerage houses have
also given target prices and ratings for some stocks. So, before starting the discussion on what are the
news and which stocks are there,
I would like to say
that if you have not subscribed to our channel,
please subscribe and
also press the bell icon. First of all, we will talk about the market share
of Artist Chapter company Infosys.
Today, it is
seeing a decline in the market time. There is a decline of 1.5%.
If we
talk about its performance in the last 5 days, then there is a
decline of more than 12%. Let us
tell you that recently the company
released its quarter four results. The
profit of the company in this was
not as per the experts' estimates, it was less than that, due to which its market
share is seeing a decline. Today,
news came that Liqui has increased its holdings
in this company on quarter.
Liqui's share holding in Infosys has increased by
7.5 percent plus one.  The percentage which
increased to
8.01.09% in the quarter means that the stock
bought in Infosys in the quarter. However, if we
talk about foreign investors,
they have sold. Currently, the
total share holding of foreign investors in the March quarter
is 35.8% which
was 36.28% in quarter 3. If we
talk about institutional investors,
their holding is also seen decreasing. The
holding of institutional investors in quarter 3 was
69.5% which has reduced to
68.95% in the quarter. If we talk about some other aspects, then
you can see that the
mutual fund investors who are the top
investors in Infosys are ICC
Prudential
and HDFC Mutual Fund and SBI
Mutual Fund, Ooty Mutual Fund and Aditya
Birla Sun Life Trustee. These are the top
investors of Infosys. After the quarter four results of the company
came out, some brokerage houses have
also given ratings and also told its target.
Speaking of BNP, they have
given Infosys a 'Bike' rating and a
target price of 1675. Furthermore, another piece of news
related to the IT sector is emerging. This
news is quoting Thinktech. While
authentic
approval hasn't yet arrived, it's being reported
that the Cabinet has approved the National Quantum Mission. It will
most benefit
artist-led companies that are
working to invest in this field.
6,000 crore has been allocated for this mission,
meaning it can be allocated.
Such news is circulating, citing Shatrughan. Companies working
in the field of quantum technology can benefit significantly from
this. Companies that are
already showing interest in this field are therefore
significant. This could potentially benefit
these companies in the future.
Meanwhile, the
lack of positive results from IT giants TCS and Infosys is
also impacting technology stocks. The
company will release its quarterly
results in a day or two, but
before that, its stocks are experiencing significant pressure.
You can see that  It is seeing a
decline of more than 2% during market hours.
This video is market-type; the
situation may change in the future.
[Music]
Regarding its
revenue, it may
see quarter-on-quarter growth of 1.3%.
Apart from this, if we talk about
other forecast houses, their
expectation is that the company's revenue may
see 17.5% quarter-on-quarter growth
and there may be a
decline of 0.6% in the interest.
If we talk about the estimated price of this company, it is being
said that
6.3% quarter-on-quarter growth may be seen.
Currently, there is pressure on its shares in the market.
Although there is minor
pressure, but the company has informed that
its voting meeting will be held on the 4th, in which the results will be
announced.
Along with the announcement of the quarter-on-quarter results, dividend will
also be considered. If there is any possibility of dividend,
then dividend will also be announced.
Due to this, Fox can be mine. You
can keep an eye on it.  If we talk about
Zomato, two news are being seen in Zomato as well.
Currently,
its shares are seeing a 2% decline in the market hours.
Some brokerage houses have also given ratings regarding this and have
also given the target price.
Yes, UBS has given a negative rating to it
and has given its target price of ₹80,
although the target price has been reduced.
Earlier, it had given its target price of ₹90,
due to this, this share can also remain in the red. Another
news is being seen in this
that the
exchange had asked it
why it is closing blank kit stores, on this the
company has also given its answer. The
company has said that most of its stores which were
closed have now been opened
and work has started there.
It has also said that there is no material impact on
any operations or financial performance. Since then,
its shares are
seeing a decline. Apart from this, if
we talk about ICC Lombard, its shares are
currently under pressure. Today in this  A
decline of more than 4.5% is being seen in it.
Some
brokerage houses have
given rating regarding this and its target price has also been
told
and its target price has been told as 1560, whereas
Morgan Style has given rating regarding this
and its target price has been
told as 1400 rupees. UPS has also
given a buy rating regarding this and its target
price has been told as ₹1400 at ₹45 as per share.
GP Morgan has also maintained its neutral
rating and its
target price has been told as 1160. If we talk about Just Dial
's stock, then pressure is being seen on it today as well.
Currently, a
decline of around 1.5% is being seen in the market.
Some brokerage houses have
given rating regarding this and its target price has also been told.
Citi has maintained its buy rating
and its target
price has also been given at 815. Whereas if we talk about
Title Company's stock, then today
slight pressure was seen in its shares as well,
although today the company had
also made a high of 2595 in the market time.  Kotak
Institutional Activities has given it an add
rating and a target price of
₹2,700, while
CLS has given it a buy rating and a
target price of ₹3,150.
Furthermore, United
Spirits Limited is currently under
pressure.
Debt percentage is declining during the market hours. Brokerages have
also
given it a rating and a target price.
McQuarrie has
maintained a perform rating and a target price of
₹650. Therefore, this stock
could also remain in focus. You
can keep an eye on it. Talking about India, it had a
strong start yesterday, but has seen a decline in the last few days.
Currently, it is also
seeing a rating and a target
price. GP
Morgan has
maintained an overweight rating and has
given a target price of ₹290.
Talking about Titagarh Wagons Limited, its stocks are
seeing tremendous movement today.
Currently, the stock is
running at a profit of around 2% during market time.
Regarding this also, the
security has given a bike rating and has
given a target price of 404, so you
can keep an eye on this also. If we talk about the
stock of CMS Info System Limited,
then currently a
gain of around 2% is being seen in it during market time. The news in this is
that the
company has secured 30% of its ATMs
which are in India. The
security provided to them is a software,
so you can keep an eye on this also.